dailyfreepsd.com 2013-06-21

# » Privacy PolicyFree PSD,Vector,Icons,Graphics

Privacy Policy

Dailyfreepsd.com takes your privacy seriously.  
Dailyfreepsd.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site. Please read the following to learn more about how we protect and respect your personal privacy while logged into our web server.

Advertisers Third party Advertising 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

Below are links to the privacy policies of the advertising networks used by Dailyfreepsd.com:

Third Party Cookies 

Cookies are small files that contain information that a website uses to store user preferences and settings. You can reset your browser to control cookies; however, some Crawler services may not function properly if cookies are refused. Searches using alternate search engines such as MSN, Google, and Yahoo through the Crawler toolbar are relayed through our servers. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

External Links 

Our site may contain links to other sites. We will make every effort to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy. However, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by organizations sponsoring these other sites.

Spam 

The operators of this web site do not participate in the practice of spamming. Spamming is the sending of bulk, unsolicited email. Visitors who submit content to the web site may opt out of having their email address posted on dailyfreepsd.com web pages.

Contacting dailyfreepsd.com

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy statement or the practices of this web site, you can contact us:support@dailyfreepsd.com.

_We reserve the right to change this policy at any time by notifying visitors of the existence of the new privacy policy._

No tags for this post. 

The design resources of this site are gathered by users and public sources on the internet. Not all of the resources are allowed for commercial use please contact the author for detail.If resources have violated your copyright, please contact us so that we can delete a timely manner to protect your copyright!
